Guide to the Trumbull College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1964-2012 Maintained by the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Trumbull College, Yale University, student records for the Classes of 1964-2012 maintained by the dean
1961-2012
RU 222
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
124.25
(185 boxes)
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Trumbull College, Yale University.
Trumbull College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-N-1 (YRG 13-N-1), Records of the dean of Trumbull College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Trumbull College, Yale University.
College students; Trumbull College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Student records for the Class of 1964, Accession 19ND-A-343
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2040
- Student records for the Class of 1965, Accession 19ND-A-344
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
- Student records for the Class of 1966, Accession 19ND-A-345
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2042
- Student records for the Class of 1967, Accession 19ND-A-346
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2043
- Student records for the Class of 1968, Accession 19ND-A-347
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2044
- Student records for the Class of 1969, Accession 19ND-A-348
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2045
- Student records for the Class of 1970, Accession 19ND-A-349
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2046
- Impounded student records for the Classes of 1975-1978, Accession 1975-A-018
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
- Student records for the Classes of 1971-1972, Accession 1977-A-019
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2048
- Student records for the Classes of 1973-1974, Accession 1979-A-046
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2050
- Student records for the Class of 1975, Accession 1981-A-042
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2051
- Student records for the Class of 1976, Accession 1982-A-040
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2052
  Scope and Contents
  * Personal recommendations inserted into file
- Student records for the Class of 1977, Accession 1983-A-068
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2053
  Related Materials
  Files of students withdrawn from the class of 1977 are in RU 222, Accession 1983-A-069.
- Student records for ex-students in the Class of 1977, Accession 1983-A-069
  Restricted until January 1, 2053
  General
  Student files of the graduates of the class of 1977 are in RU 222, Accession 1983-A-068.
- Student records for the Class of 1978, Accession 1983-A-070
  - WITHDRAWN
- Student records for the Class of 1979, Accession 1984-A-043
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1980, Accession 1985-A-025
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
  - Withdrawn from Yale
- Student records for the Class of 1981, Accession 1987-A-014
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
  - Withdrawn from Yale College
- Student records for the Class of 1982, Accession 1988-A-003
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
  - Withdrawn from Yale College
- Student records for the Class of 1983, Accession 1988-A-110
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
  - Withdrawn from Yale College
  - Class Information (Box 9, Folder 95)
- Student records for the Class of 1984, Accession 1989-A-115
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  - Withdrawn from Yale College
- Student records for the Class of 1985, Accession 1991-A-014
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2061
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Classes of 1986-1987, Accession 1991-A-102
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
  - Class of 1986
    - Withdrawn
  - Class of 1987
    - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1988, Accession 1992-A-011
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
- Student records for the Class of 1989, Accession 1993-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
- Student records for the Class of 1990, Accession 1994-A-019
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
  - Withdrew
- Student records for the Class of 1991, Accession 1995-A-026
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
  - Withdrew
- Student records for the Class of 1992, Accession 1996-A-014
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
  - Withdrew
- Student records for the Class of 1993, Accession 1998-A-014
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
  - Withdrew, 1989-1993
- Student records for the Class of 1994, Accession 1999-A-005
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - Freshperson letters, 1974 (Box 4)
- Student records for the Class of 1995, Accession 2000-A-017
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
- Student records for the Class of 1996, Accession 2001-A-049
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
- Student records for the Class of 1997, Accession 2002-A-069
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2073
- Student records for the Class of 1998, Accession 2003-A-019
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
- Student records for the Class of 1999, Accession 2004-A-034
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
- Student records for the Class of 2000, Accession 2005-A-155
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
  - Withdrawn Students (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Student records for the Class of 2001, Accession 2005-A-168
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 2002, Accession 2007-A-017
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2078
- Student records for the Class of 2003, Accession 2011-A-063
  Restricted until January 1, 2082
- Student records for the Class of 2004, Accession 2011-A-064
- Student records for the Class of 2005, Accession 2012-A-097
  Restricted until January 1, 2080
- Student records for the Class of 2006, Accession 2013-A-011
  Restricted until January 1, 2081
- Student records for the Class of 2007, Accession 2014-A-039
- Student records for the Class of 2008, Accession 2014-A-080
  Restricted until January 1, 2083
  - Freshman Counselors Class of 2008, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Student records for the Class of 2009, Accession 2016-A-002
  Records are restricted until January 1, 2084 due to University policy set by the Yale Corporation.
- Student records for the Class of 2010, Accession 2017-A-002
  Restricted until January 1, 2076
- Student records for the Class of 2011, Accession 2017-A-068
  Restricted until January 1, 2087
- Student records for the Class of 2012, Accession 2018-A-079
  Restricted until January 1, 2088
  - Class of 2012
    - Adusumilli, Arjun, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Allen, Chelsea, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Al-Qasimi, Farah, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Amar, Shivani, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Aronson, Lucas, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Avini, Mitrah, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Baig, Minhal, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bao, Adam, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bernhardt, Austin, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Birukova, Maria, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Brinzevich, Daria, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Bryant, Alex, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Bystron, Rene, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Call, Winfield, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Cesar, Alexia, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Chandra, Daniel, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Chauvin, Carl, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Chesky, Matthew, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Clark, Lindsay, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Coates, Evan, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Confino, Jordana, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Connors, Shannon, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Costopoulos, Philip, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Damrosch, Peter, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Daniels, Bradley, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - De Feis, Carly, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - deFeo, Courtney, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - DiBenedetto, Egidio, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Dixon, Samantha, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Foreman, Clifford, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Friedman, Raphaella, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Gaytan Lemus, Ruben, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Gidado, Travis, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Gocksch, Michael, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Grody, Evin, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Halliday, Charles, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Hioki, Tami, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Homans-Turnbull, Marian, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Howard, Thomas, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Hyde, Hayes, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Ilter, Sinan, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Jimenez, Eva, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Jin, Qiuyu, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Kelly, Gabriella, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Kerr, Alexandra, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Khan, Uzra, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Kim, Andrew, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Kim, Janice, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Lee, Conrad, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Lee, Jin Won, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Lee, Melissa, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Lehner, Verena, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Lemle, Julia, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Liles, Robert, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Linton, Diana, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Liu, Alex, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Liu, Benjamine, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Locati, Niccolo, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - London, Rachel, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Lyons, David Greg, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Marin, Isabel, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Martinez, Jose, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - McCreary, Scott, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Mehmedovic, Sabina, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Moritz, William, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Naimi, Shahla, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Naman, Julia, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Overstreet, Anthony, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Oyler, Lauren, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Paniagua, Agustin, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Park, Ryan, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Partouche, Hugo, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Peters, Elizabeth, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Pham, Hai, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Pineda, Paloma, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Pitoniak, Patrick, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Powers, Jonathan, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Progios, Panagiotis, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Quartey, Emmanuel, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Rivers, Mackenzie, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Roberts, John, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Rosenblum, Amy, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Rubin, Courtney, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Rudnicka, Ewelina, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Sackey, Cecily, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Schlossberg, Tatiana, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Schottenfeld, Joseph, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Shoko, Tatenda, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Singh, Nandini, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Singleton, Michael, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Sullivan, Sarah, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Ternus, Brendan, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Terrien, Jules, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Tran, Lisa, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Treger, Rebecca, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Wallace, Claire, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Weaver, Cynthia, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Wilson, Maxim, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Witthuhn, Jennifer, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Yim, Margaret, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Xu, Liangsha, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 40)